Thank you,Wendy.
谢谢你, Wendy.
Yes,we've had a very good year.
对, 我们这一年经营得很好.
We've managed to control our costs,as you can see.
我们设法控制了成本, 正如您所看到的那样.
They're actually down 7%.
成本实际下降了7%.
Not bad.But of course you're expected to do that.
干得不错, 不过这是你们应该做到的.
And we've changed our advertising.
我们也改变了广告的方式.
We think that's helped new business.
我们认为这促进了新的业务.
New business has grown 10% since last January.
从去年1月开始,新业务增长了10%.
Not bad.
干得不错.
With the industry in its current state,I venture to say it's quite good.
考虑到这个行业目前的状况, 我冒昧说一句, 这已经很好了.
Here's your water,sir.
先生. 您的水.
I'm not interestecd in the standard report,Anne.
我对这种常规报告不感兴趣, Anne.
I can read.
我自己可以读.
By all means.
那当然.
Is there anything else I can answer for you then?
还有什么别的问题需要我解答吗?
I've heard about the programs,Anne.
我听说了那些项目, Anne.
Employee groups,the marketing.
雇员小组和营销.
And I want to know who's responsible.
我想知道是谁在负责.
I see.
我明白了.
We have many other hotels,you know.
你要知道,我们还有许多其他的饭店.
And I want them all to do as well as this one.
我希望他们全部都能做得像这家一样好.